const questions = [
    {
        question: "jock lit hip goo keys",
        answer: "chocolate chip cookies"
    },
    {
        question: "high dance eek",
        answer: "hide and seek"
    },
    {
        question: "reef idge her ate her",
        answer: "refrigerator"
    },
    {
        question: "is bunch pops queer pans",
        answer: "spongebob squarepants"
    },
    {
        question: "shack cough alt raids",
        answer: "jack of all trades"
    },
    {
        question: "poe day tote ships",
        answer: "potato chips"
    },
    {
        question: "ha minch ease",
        answer: "ham and cheese"
    },
    {
        question: "she is burg her",
        answer: "cheeseburger"
    },
    {
        question: "highs creek own",
        answer: "ice cream cone"
    },
    {
        question: "jock lit prow knees",
        answer: "chocolate brownies"
    },
    {
        question: "hap pulled use",
        answer: "apple juice"
    },
    {
        question: "jik hin ugh its",
        answer: "chicken nuggets"
    },
    {
        question: "fur rose in yoke hurt",
        answer: "frozen yogurt"
    },
    {
        question: "ewe night ted king dumb",
        answer: "united kingdom"
    },
    {
        question: "veer off mess sing oat",
        answer: "fear of missing out"
    },
    {
        question: "ban gake sand sir rup",
        answer: "pancakes and syrup"
    },
    {
        question: "sad herd day",
        answer: "saturday"
    },
    {
        question: "tay cove ache a shun",
        answer: "take a vacation"
    },
    {
        question: "abe autumn lisp hit",
        answer: "a bottomless pit"
    },
    {
        question: "sew fiat tune yawn",
        answer: "soviet union"
    },
    {
        question: "aid own hutton call fee",
        answer: "a donut and coffee"
    },
    {
        question: "mise whims hoot",
        answer: "my swimsuit"
    },
    {
        question: "abe an an appeal",
        answer: "a banana peel"
    },
    {
        question: "abe ax tree tally",
        answer: "a backstreet alley"
    },
    {
        question: "saw hift talk ohs",
        answer: "soft tacos"
    },
    {
        question: "notch hose anch ease",
        answer: "nachos and cheese"
    },
    {
        question: "bep her own knee peas uh",
        answer: "pepperoni pizza"
    },
    {
        question: "ma car own knee anch ease",
        answer: "macaroni and cheese"
    },
    {
        question: "ping hut bud her",
        answer: "peanut butter"
    },
    {
        question: "dez pus seed hoe",
        answer: "despacito"
    },
    {
        question: "ail huck each arm",
        answer: "a lucky charm"
    },
]

module.exports = questions;